{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Au_Secours!",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance produced the film Au Secours!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8822827935218811,
            "question": "Who produced the film Au Secours!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7553756237030029,
            "question": "When was the film Au Secours! likely produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6491712927818298,
            "question": "Is Abel Gance known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6065075993537903,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Au Secours! about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5923152565956116,
            "question": "Where was the film Au Secours! filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5721530318260193,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5119388103485107,
            "question": "What impact did the film Au Secours! have on cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4872644245624542,
            "question": "What genre is the film Au Secours! likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42510899901390076,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33227428793907166,
            "question": "Were there any famous actors in the film Au Secours!"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance produced the film Au Secours!",
            "html": "yago_4151_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film directed by Abel Gance?",
            "html": "yago_4151_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Au Secours! likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_4151_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did the film Au Secours! have on cinema?",
            "html": "yago_4151_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4151_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4151/re-ranker-msmarco/110.txt mentions Abel Gance and Max Linder collaborating on the film \"Au Secours!\".\n* The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4151/re-ranker-msmarco/84.txt explicitly states that Abel Gance directed the film \"Au secours!\", which is also known as \"Au Secours!\".\n\nBased on this information, I conclude that:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Abel Gance being involved in the production of the film \"Au Secours!\" and detail his role as a director. Therefore, it is correct to state that Abel Gance produced the film \"Au Secours!\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}